<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <VRE_Ecstasy.label>екстаз</VRE_Ecstasy.label>
  <VRE_Ecstasy.description>Carriers of this gene can psychically connect with the target briefly, granting them a sense of ecstasy and making them fall in love with the caster.</VRE_Ecstasy.description>

  <VRE_FilterInfection.label>інфекція фільтра</VRE_FilterInfection.label>
  <VRE_FilterInfection.description>Carriers of this gene have special glands in their mouths that allow them to filter infected blood from the clean blood.</VRE_FilterInfection.description>

  <VRE_Hemosmosis.label>гемовичавлювання</VRE_Hemosmosis.label>
  <VRE_Hemosmosis.description>Carriers of this gene are able to drain blood from their environment, provided there is blood to be drained there.</VRE_Hemosmosis.description>

  <VRE_ToxicCloud.label>токсична хмара</VRE_ToxicCloud.label>
  <VRE_ToxicCloud.description>Carriers of this gene are able to excrete a thick toxic smoke from special organic reservoirs in their lungs. Tox gas is deadly to almost every creature.</VRE_ToxicCloud.description>

  <VRE_HeartCrush.label>серцевинос</VRE_HeartCrush.label>
  <VRE_HeartCrush.description>Носій цього гена має особливі адреналінові залози, які даю змогу їм знаходити серце суперника і виривати його в шаленій люті.</VRE_HeartCrush.description>

  <VRE_ViscuousGoo.label>в'язка слизь</VRE_ViscuousGoo.label>
  <VRE_ViscuousGoo.description>Carriers grow glands in the neck that generate and store a thick goo. They can spit it over long distances and cover several people in a viscous goo that will slow them down.</VRE_ViscuousGoo.description>

  <VRE_Resurrect.label>воскресіння</VRE_Resurrect.label>
  <VRE_Resurrect.description>Carriers have a reserve of unique resurrector archites which can infuse a corpse, rebuild degenerated tissue and kickstart the vital processes. This brings the dead back to life - though possibly with health issues. This can only be done very rarely, and comes at a steep hemogen cost.</VRE_Resurrect.description>

</LanguageData>